Guide to the United Board for Christian Higher Education in Asia Records - Addendum B
Yale University Divinity School Library
- United Board Consolidated General File, Series II
  - Logan, Rufus T., 1964-1977 (Box 48, Folder 707)
  - Loh, J. Wei-ping, 1971-1974 (Box 49, Folder 708)
  - Long, Charles H., 1961-1977 (Box 49, Folder 708)
  - Longview Community Church, WA, 1964-1968 (Box 49, Folder 709)
  - Lopulisa, Shirley Cloyes and Robert, 1976-1979 (Box 49, Folder 710)
  - Los Altos Union Church, Ca, 1959-1962 (Box 49, Folder 711)
  - Loucks, Emerson, 1965-1968 (Box 49, Folder 712)
  - Loucks, Harold H., 1966-1979 (Box 49, Folder 713)
  - Lovejoy, Allen and Jean, 1963-1979 (Box 49, Folder 714)
  - Lovett, Sidney, 1966-1977 (Box 49, Folder 715)
  - Lowe, Pardee, 1964-1975 (Box 49, Folder 715)
  - Lowenberg, Edwin C., 1970-1971 (Box 49, Folder 716)
  - Lu, Chin - Estate of, 1973-1976 (Box 49, Folder 717)
  - Lucas, John, 1975-1976 (Box 49, Folder 718)
  - Luce, Henry III, 1961-1981 (Box 49, Folder 719)
  - Luce, Henry R., 1963-1967 (Box 49, Folder 720)
  - Luce, Henry - Foundation, 1971-1979 (Box 49, Folder 721,722)
  - Luce, Sheldon R., 1964-1978 (Box 49, Folder 723)
  - Luidens, Edwin, 1966-1979 (Box 50, Folder 724)
  - Lutz, Lenore H., 1965-1977 (Box 50, Folder 725)
  - Lynn, Robert A., 1965 (Box 50, Folder 725)
  - Lyon, E. Wilson and Carolyn, 1965-1979 (Box 50, Folder 726,727)
  - Mac - Maz (Box 50, Folder 728-732)
  - Me - Mw (Box 51, Folder 733-739)
  - MacInnis, Donald E., 1970-1979 (Box 51, Folder 740)
  - MacLean, Marie - Estate of, 1960-1963 (Box 52, Folder 741)
  - McBrier, Edwin M. - Trust, 1963-1978 (Box 52, Folder 742)
  - McCall, John T. and Gertrude - Estate of, 1969-1975 (Box 52, Folder 743)
  - McCloud, Oscar, 1974,1976 (Box 52, Folder 744)
  - McClure, Robert B., 1965-1979 (Box 52, Folder 744)
  - McComb, Donald, 1972-1979 (Box 52, Folder 745)
  - McCormick, Nettie Fowler - Fund, 1976 (Box 52, Folder 746)
  - McCreless, S. E., 1962-1978 (Box 52, Folder 746)
  - McCune, Shannon, 1966-1976 (Box 52, Folder 747)
  - McCutcheon Memorial Scholarship, 1965-1974 (Box 52, Folder 748)
  - McEachern, Vernon and Dorothy, 1968-1969 (Box 52, Folder 749)
  - McGraw-Hill Foundation, 1979 (Box 52, Folder 750)
  - McKeever, Porter and Susan, 1965-1979 (Box 52, Folder 751)
  - McKenzie, Hillis S., 1963-1974 (Box 52, Folder 752)
  - McKinney, William Ayer, 1958-1963 (Box 52, Folder 753)
  - McLaughlin, Marilyn Crosswhite, 1962-1967 (Box 52, Folder 754)
  - McMullen, John S. and Robert J., 1962-1968 (Box 52, Folder 755)
  - McNear, George P. and Elizabeth, 1962-1977 (Box 52, Folder 756)
  - McNeil, Robert J. Jr. - Trust, 1966-1973 (Box 52, Folder 756)
  - McNemar, Donald W., 1968 (Box 52, Folder 757)
  - Macalester College, 1968-1970 (Box 52, Folder 758)
  - Macy, Josiah, Jr. - Foundation, 1963-1974 (Box 52, Folder 759)
  - Magdamo, Ben and Patricia, 1971-1979 (Box 53, Folder 760)
  - Magdamo, Priscilla, 1977-1978 (Box 53, Folder 761)
  - Magill, Robert N., 1971-1974 (Box 53, Folder 762)
  - Magill, Samuel H., 1968 (Box 53, Folder 763)
  - Maguire, John D., 1975-1979 (Box 53, Folder 764,765)
  - Mair, Victor Henry, 1961-1972 (Box 53, Folder 766)
  - Malaysia: Association for Promotion of Higher Education in Malaysia (APHEM), 1968-1979 (Box 53, Folder 767,768)
  - Malaysia: Genting Highlands College, 1971-1975 (Box 53, Folder 769-771)
  - Malaysia: Teoh, Jin-Inn, 1977 (Box 54, Folder 772)
  - Malone, Carroll B. and Katherine H. C., 1972-1977 (Box 54, Folder 773)
  - Manning, R. Kenneth, 1971-1977 (Box 54, Folder 774)
  - Mansfield, James L., 1962-1963 (Box 54, Folder 775)
  - Manufacturers Hanover Trust Co., 1973-1979 (Box 54, Folder 776)
  - Marcy, Eleanor N. - Trust Fund, 1945-1978 (Box 54, Folder 777)
  - Mariemont Community Church, OH, 1961-1968 (Box 54, Folder 778)
  - Markus, I. Made, 1973-1976 (Box 54, Folder 779)
  - Marquis, Sarah - Travel Service, 1973-1979 (Box 54, Folder 780)
  - Marshall, Irl H. - Scholarship Fund, 1962-1979 (Box 54, Folder 781)
  - Marty, Wayne G., 1968-1978 (Box 54, Folder 782)
  - Maruyama, Yoshio, 1974-1978 (Box 54, Folder 783)
  - Masland Foundation, 1962-1973 (Box 54, Folder 784)
  - Matthews, Clifford M. - Estate of, 1961-1964 (Box 54, Folder 785)
  - Matthias, Virginia, 1961-1974 (Box 54, Folder 786)
  - Mattox, Lois Lyon - Estate of, 1970-1972 (Box 55, Folder 787)
  - Maus, Cynthia Pearl, 1963-1970 (Box 55, Folder 788)
  - Mayfield, M. Kent, 1971-1975 (Box 55, Folder 789)
  - Maxwell, Howard B., 1973 (Box 55, Folder 790)
  - Meek Foundation, 1968-1979 (Box 55, Folder 790)
  - Mei, Yi-pao, 1971-1979 (Box 55, Folder 791)
  - Mellon, Andrew W. - Foundation, 1968-1978 (Box 55, Folder 792)
  - Memorial Minutes - (biographical sketches), 1974-1979 (Box 55, Folder 793)
  - Mennonite Central Committee, 1966-1977 (Box 55, Folder 794)
  - Mennonite Press, 1972-1979 (Box 55, Folder 795)
  - Merrill, Charles E. - Trust Fund, 1962-1979 (Box 55, Folder 796)
  - Merwin, Wallace C., 1969-1979 (Box 55, Folder 797)
  - Meuser, Edwin N., 1965-1974 (Box 55, Folder 798)
  - Meuwissen, E. J. M. / Stichting Benevolentia, 1976-1978 (Box 55, Folder 799)
  - Miami Shores Community Church, FL, 1959-1968 (Box 55, Folder 800)
  - Mihran, G. Arthur, 1976-1978 (Box 55, Folder 801)
  - Miller, Edward C., 1971-1972 (Box 55, Folder 802)
  - Miller, Margaret, 1964-1970 (Box 56, Folder 803)
  - Miller, Marjorie, 1974-1979 (Box 56, Folder 804)
  - Millett, Fred J., 1971-1979 (Box 56, Folder 804)
  - Milliken, Seth M. - Estate of, 1957-1966 (Box 56, Folder 805)
  - Milner, Clyde A., 1964-1965 (Box 56, Folder 806)
  - Mills, Ralph J., 1974-1978 (Box 56, Folder 807)
  - Minear, Anita, 1966-1970 (Box 56, Folder 808)
  - Mission boards: -American Baptist, 1965-1980 (Box 56, Folder 809-811)
  - Mission boards: -Christian Church (Disciples of Christ), 1964-1980 (Box 56, Folder 812-815)
  - Mission boards: -Episcopal, 1975-1979 (Box 56, Folder 816)
  - Mission boards: -Lutheran Church in America, 1960-1979 (Box 56, Folder 817-818)
  - Mission boards: -Presbyterian Church in Canada, 1964-1978 (Box 57, Folder 819)
  - Mission boards: -Presbyterian Church in U.S.A., 1964-1979 (Box 57, Folder 820)
  - Mission boards: -Reformed Church in America, 1960-1979 (Box 57, Folder 821)
  - Mission boards: -United Church of Canada, 1964-1980 (Box 57, Folder 822-825)
  - Mission boards: -United Church of Christ, 1965-1979 (Box 57, Folder 826-827)
  - Mission boards: -United Church of Christ (Box 58, Folder 828-830)
  - Mission boards:-United Methodist Church, 1970-1980 (Box 58, Folder 831-834)
  - Mission boards: -United Methodist Church antecedent: Evangelical United Brethren, 1964-1969 (Box 59, Folder 835)
  - Mission boards: -United Presbyterian Church U.S.A., 1966-1980 (Box 59, Folder 836-839)
  - Missions Boards personnel, 1964-1975 (Box 59, Folder 840-841)
  - Moe, David, 1965 (Box 60, Folder 842)
  - Mook, Telfer and Jane, 1969-1979 (Box 60, Folder 843)
  - Moore, Elisabeth Luce -Correspondence, 1971-1979 (Box 60, Folder 844-846)
  - Moore, Elisabeth Luce -Biographical documentation, 1960-1979 (Box 60, Folder 847-849)
  - Morgan, Bruce B., 1964-1965 (Box 60, Folder 850)
  - Morgan, Julia - Fund, 1972 (Box 60, Folder 851)
  - Morrill, Paul H., 1965-1969 (Box 60, Folder 852)
  - Mortensen, Erik, 1975-1976 (Box 60, Folder 853)
  - Mortgage on 693-699 First Avenue, NYC, 1938-1961 (Box 60, Folder 854)
  - Morton-Smith, Maida, 1961-1978 (Box 60, Folder 855)
  - Moses, David G., 1965-1968 (Box 60, Folder 856)
  - Mott, George Fox, 1967-1979 (Box 60, Folder 857)
  - Mowry, Loyd, 1963-1968 (Box 60, Folder 858)
  - Moxcey, Mary E. - Estate of, 1967-1975 (Box 61, Folder 859)
  - Muilenburg, John P., 1967-1968 (Box 61, Folder 859)
  - Mungello, David E., 1974-1979 (Box 61, Folder 860)
  - Munn, Eufemia C. and Merton D., 1965-1975 (Box 61, Folder 861)
  - Murray, Donald M., 1972-1973 (Box 61, Folder 862)
  - Murty, K. Rajeswari, 1975-1976 (Box 61, Folder 863)
  - Mutual Benefit Life Insurance, 1976-1979 (Box 61, Folder 863)
  - Myong, Jae Hwi, 1965-1968 (Box 61, Folder 864)
  - Na - Ny (Box 61, Folder 865-868)
  - Nance, Walter B., 1965 (Box 61, Folder 869)
  - National Cash Register, 1976-1979 (Box 61, Folder 870)
  - National Council of Churches of Christ in the U.S.A./ Division of Overseas Ministries, 1977-1981 (Box 62, Folder 871-884)
  - Documentation of Executive Committee, Committee for East Asia and the Pacific, Southern Asia program, finance, Human Rights Office, Intermedia
  - NCCCUSA / Division of Overseas Missions, 1977-1979 (Box 63, Folder 885-891)
  - Japan-North America Commission on Co-operative Mission, Leadership Development Program, Committee on Overseas Personnel, Philippine Joint Action Group, Southern Asia program, Unit Committee
  - Netherlands - Dutch Working Group for Satya Wacana, 1976-1978 (Box 63, Folder 892)
  - Netherlands - Interkerkelijke Coordinatie Commissie und Ontwikkelingshulp (ICCO), 1973-1982 (Box 63, Folder 893)
  - New, Mrs. Waysung (Y.T. Zee), 1964-1981 (Box 63, Folder 894-896)
  - New Asia College - Library Survey (Frick), 1964 (Box 63, Folder 897)
  - New Day Publishers, 1971-1979 (Box 64, Folder 898)
  - New York Bank for Savings, 1971-1979 (Box 64, Folder 900)
  - New York Life Insurance Co., 1964-1976 (Box 64, Folder 901)
  - New York State Department of Labor, 1973-1978 (Box 64, Folder 902)
  - New York State and New York City Tax Exemptions, 1954-1971 (Box 64, Folder 903)
  - New York State Department of Law, 1960-1972 (Box 64, Folder 904)
  - New York University / SUNY, 1971-1978 (Box 64, Folder 905)
  - Newberry College, 1971-1974 (Box 64, Folder 906)
  - Ng, Wai Yee, 1973-1974 (Box 64, Folder 907)
  - Noble, Hubert C., 1966-1974 (Box 64, Folder 908)
  - Nordstrom, Joseph A., 1965-1966 (Box 64, Folder 909)
  - Noren, Loren, 1971-1978 (Box 64, Folder 910)
  - North, Eric M., 1963-1980 (Box 64, Folder 911)
  - North Carolina State Board of Public Welfare, 1955-1967 (Box 64, Folder 912)
  - Northern Illinois University, 1973 (Box 64, Folder 913)
  - Northup, Robert W., 1971-1979 (Box 64, Folder 913)
  - Nottingham, William, 1976-1979 (Box 64, Folder 914)
  - Nuveen, John - Benevolent Trust, 1972-1979 (Box 64, Folder 915)
  - Oa - Or (Box 64, Folder 916-917)
  - Os - Ox (Box 65, Folder 918)
  - Oberlin-Shansi Memorial Association, 1964-1979 (Box 65, Folder 919)
  - Obor Foundation, 1977-1979 (Box 65, Folder 920)
  - Oh, Sei Chull, 1971-1975 (Box 65, Folder 921)
  - Olin Foundation, 1968-1974 (Box 65, Folder 922)
  - Olmstead, Robert J., 1961-1969 (Box 65, Folder 922)
  - Ong, Shao-er, 1969-1979 (Box 65, Folder 923)
  - Orndorff, J. K. and Harriet C., 1967-1979 (Box 65, Folder 924)
  - Orwig, James P., 1976-1979 (Box 65, Folder 925)
  - Osborn, Mary E. - Estate of, 1967-1976 (Box 65, Folder 926)
  - Osborne, B. L., 1965 (Box 65, Folder 927)
  - Overby, Carl H., 1965 (Box 65, Folder 929)
  - Overhiser, Miranda A. - Estate of, 1949-1957 (Box 65, Folder 928)
  - Overholt, William A., 1965-1969 (Box 65, Folder 929)
  - Overseas Educational Service, n.d. (Box 65, Folder 930)
  - Owens, Paul Joseph, 1971-1979 (Box 65, Folder 930)
  - Pa (Box 65, Folder 931-933)
  - Pe - Py (Box 66, Folder 934-938)
  - Pace, Frank Jr. - Foundation, 1964-1973 (Box 66, Folder 939)
  - Packanack Community Church, NJ, 1962-1974 (Box 66, Folder 940)
  - Padelford, Norman J., 1964-1979 (Box 66, Folder 941)
  - Paguia, Pauline, 1973-1976 (Box 66, Folder 942)
  - Paik, Kee Duk, 1967-1969 (Box 66, Folder 943)
  - Pakistan - Kinnaird College for Women, 1965-1979 (Box 66, Folder 944)
  - Palm, James E., 1971-1978 (Box 66, Folder 945)
  - Palmer, Robert B., 1976-1978 (Box 66, Folder 946)
  - Pamplona Plantation Co., 1973 (Box 67, Folder 947)
  - Pantejo, Edmundo A., 1965-1970 (Box 67, Folder 948)
  - Pardee, William A., 1970-1974 (Box 67, Folder 949)
  - Park, Hoon through Park, Young-Jae (Box 67, Folder 949-952)
  - Parrenas, Betty Y., 1973-1974 (Box 67, Folder 953)
  - Parsonage, Robert, 1978-1979 (Box 67, Folder 953)
  - Patty, Ernest N. and Virginia, 1967-1976 (Box 67, Folder 954)
  - Pearson, John D., 1974-1979 (Box 67, Folder 955)
  - Peel Bequest, 1955-1973 (Box 67, Folder 956)
  - Pei, I. M., 1965-1979 (Box 67, Folder 957)
  - Peking American School, 1968-1969 (Box 67, Folder 958)
  - Penney Memorial Church, FL, 1970-1979 (Box 67, Folder 959)
  - Perspective Asia, 1972-1974 (Box 67, Folder 960)
  - Perkins, George W., 1961-1979 (Box 67, Folder 961)
  - Pew Memorial Trust, 1957-1974 (Box 67, Folder 962)
  - Phelps, Dryden, 1963-1977 (Box 67, Folder 963)
  - Phenix, Philip, 1964-1975 (Box 67, Folder 964)
  - Phi Beta Kappa, 1964 (Box 67, Folder 964)
  - Philippines: -General, 1963-1979 (Box 67, Folder 965)
  - Philippines: -Accrediting Association of Schools, Colleges, Universities, 1967-1970 (Box 67, Folder 966)
  - Philippines: -Apayao Christian Academy, 1976-1977 (Box 67, Folder 967)
  - Philippines: -Angeles University, 1976 (Box 68, Folder 968)
  - Philippines: -"An Appraisal of the Protestant Christian Effort in Higher Education in Asia - Philippines", 1968 (Box 68, Folder 969)
  - Philippines: -Association of Christian Schools and Colleges (ACSC), 1971-1979 (Box 68, Folder 970-976)
  - Philippines: -Ateneo de Manila University, 1972-1979 (Box 68, Folder 977)
  - Philippines: -Catholic Educational Association of the Philippines, 1977-1978 (Box 68, Folder 978)
  - Philippines: -Dansalan College - Lloyd and Maisie Van Vactor, 1969-1979 (Box 69, Folder 979)
  - Philippines: -Dansalan College - Research Center (Peter Gowing), 1974-1979 (Box 69, Folder 980)
  - Philippines: -Education - Church-related, 1964-1969 (Box 69, Folder 981)
  - Philippines: -Fund for Assistance to Private Education, 1976-1978 (Box 69, Folder 982)
  - Philippines: -Interchurch Commission on Medical Care, 1963-1973 (Box 69, Folder 983)
  - Philippines: -Inter-institutional Consortium, 1975-1980 (Box 69, Folder 984-986)
  - Philippines: -Maasin, College of, 1973-1979 (Box 69, Folder 987)
  - Philippines: -Mindanao Educational Conference, 1972 (Box 69, Folder 988)
  - Philippines: -Mindanao State University, 1962-1974 (Box 69, Folder 989)
  - Philippines: -National Rural Life Center, 1978 (Box 69, Folder 989)
  - Philippines: -Philippine Consulate General, 1965-1973 (Box 69, Folder 990)
  - Philippines: -Philippine Studies Council, 1973-1974 (Box 69, Folder 990)
  - Philippines: -Philippine Wesleyan College, 1974-1978 (Box 69, Folder 991)
  - Philippines: -Philippine Women's University, 1968-1969 (Box 69, Folder 992)
  - Philippines: -St. Joseph College, 1974 (Box 69, Folder 993)
  - Philippines: -Tanjay College, 1970-1973 (Box 69, Folder 994)
  - Philippines: -Union Christian College, 1972 (Box 69, Folder 994)
  - Philippines: -Union Theological Seminary, 1970-1979 (Box 70, Folder 995-996)
  - Philippines: -United Church of Christ in the Philippines, 1967-1979 (Box 70, Folder 997)
  - Philippines: -United Missionary Office, 1971-1979 (Box 70, Folder 998)
  - Philippines: -University of the Philippines at Los Banos;University of the Philippines, Quezon City;-University of Santo Thomas, 1973-1979 (Box 70, Folder 999)
  - Philippines: -University of San Carlos, 1972-1979 (Box 70, Folder 1000)
  - Phillips, Ellis L. - Foundation, 1959-1979 (Box 70, Folder 1001)
  - Piedmont Community Church, CA, 1960-1969 (Box 70, Folder 1002)
  - Pierson, A. Chadwick, 1964 (Box 70, Folder 1003)
  - Piet, David and Nancy, 1972-1974 (Box 70, Folder 1004)
  - Pint, John and Susanna, 1972-1975 (Box 70, Folder 1005)
  - Pittsburgh (Sewickley) Committee, 1971-1976 (Box 70, Folder 1006)
  - Plimpton, Francis T. P., 1970-1983 (Box 70, Folder 1007)
  - Pomona Study Abroad Program, 1969 (Box 70, Folder 1008)
  - Poole, Robert R., 1968 (Box 70, Folder 1008)
  - Poppen, Alvin J., 1976-1977 (Box 70, Folder 1008)
  - Porter, Luz S., 1961-1978 (Box 71, Folder 1009)
  - Potter, Neil, 1973-1974 (Box 71, Folder 1010)
  - Potter, Taylor M., 1967-1979 (Box 71, Folder 1011)
  - Powell, Charles L., 1969 (Box 71, Folder 1012)
  - Powell, William, 1965-1970 (Box 71, Folder 1013)
  - Presbyterian Historical Society, 1969-1973 (Box 71, Folder 1014)
  - Prescott, Charles A. and Diane, 1968-1970 (Box 71, Folder 1015)
  - Presidents' Conferences (Asian Christian University Presidents), 1973,1975 (Box 71, Folder 1016-1017)
  - Presler, Paul E., 1965-1970 (Box 71, Folder 1018)
  - Presley, Horton, 1978-1979 (Box 71, Folder 1019)
  - Preston, William M., 1964-1979 (Box 71, Folder 1020)
  - Price-Waterhouse Co., 1965-1978 (Box 71, Folder 1021)
  - Princeton-in-Asia, 1973-1977 (Box 71, Folder 1022)
  - Profiles of United Board-related institutions, 1979 (Box 71, Folder 1023)
  - Projects approved by United Board, 1976-1979 (Box 72, Folder 1024)
  - Pusey, Nathan, 1965-1979 (Box 72, Folder 1025)
  - Pyke, James H., 1974-1976 (Box 72, Folder 1026)
  - Q (Box 72, Folder 1027)
  - Queen's College Asian Program, 1978-1988 (Box 72, Folder 1028)
  - Quon, Lily Ho - Scholarships, 1942-1979 (Box 72, Folder 1029)
  - Ra - Ry (Box 72, Folder 1030-1035)
  - Rada, Stephen E., 1978-1979 (Box 73, Folder 1036)
  - Ranson, Charles W., 1954-1977 (Box 73, Folder 1037)
  - Reader's Digest Foundation, 1970-1979 (Box 73, Folder 1038)
  - Reckard, Edgar C., 1971-1979 (Box 73, Folder 1039)
  - Reed, Alice and Harold C., 1961-1979 (Box 73, Folder 1040)
  - Reed, Mary Frances, 1964-1977 (Box 73, Folder 1041)
  - Reese, Willis L. M., 1964-1979 (Box 73, Folder 1042)
  - Reeves, Cora D. - Estate of, 1953-1963 (Box 73, Folder 1043)
  - Refo, Henry B., 1965-1979 (Box 73, Folder 1044)
  - Regional Institute of Higher Education Development (RIHED) - Singapore, 1974-1978 (Box 73, Folder 1045)
  - Religious News Service, 1968-1979 (Box 73, Folder 1046)
  - Reischauer, Edwin O., 1966-1978 (Box 73, Folder 1047)
  - Reynolds, Bruce L., 1966-1970 (Box 73, Folder 1048)
  - Reynolds, Douglas R., 1974-1977 (Box 73, Folder 1049)
  - Reynolds, Hubert, 1965-1979 (Box 73, Folder 1050)
  - Reynolds, R. S., 1961-1968 (Box 73, Folder 1051)
  - Rhee, Kyu Sun, 1972-1976 (Box 73, Folder 1052)
  - Rhee, Syngman, 1973-1979 (Box 73, Folder 1053)
  - Rhoades, J. Benton, 1970-1979 (Box 73, Folder 1054)
  - Rice, Roberta G., 1972-1976 (Box 73, Folder 1054)
  - Richards, Jack C., 1971-1978 (Box 73, Folder 1055)
  - Richelsen, Mark, 1963-1965 (Box 73, Folder 1056)
  - Rico, Modesto, 1973-1974 (Box 73, Folder 1057)
  - Rippel, Fannie - Foundation, 1961 (Box 73, Folder 1058)
  - Riverside Church, NY, 1977 (Box 73, Folder 1059)
  - Roberts, Thomas H., 1959-1966 (Box 73, Folder 1060)
  - Rockefeller Foundation, 1963-1974 (Box 74, Folder 1061)
  - Rockefeller, Laurance and Mary, 1965-1978 (Box 74, Folder 1061)
  - Roehm, Carol M., 1964-1979 (Box 74, Folder 1062)
  - Rogers, Robert A., 1973-1978 (Box 74, Folder 1062)
  - Rohlfs, Marcus, 1975-1979 (Box 74, Folder 1063)
  - Rohrman Fund, 1960-1971 (Box 74, Folder 1064)
  - Rohsenow, John S., 1979 (Box 74, Folder 1065)
  - Roosevelt Hotel, 1979 (Box 74, Folder 1066)
  - Rork, John B., 1973-1978 (Box 74, Folder 1067)
  - Rosario, Florangel Z., 1969-1970 (Box 74, Folder 1068)
  - Rosas, Nilo L., 1978 (Box 74, Folder 1068)
  - Ross, Caroline S.- Estate of, 1960 (Box 74, Folder 1069)
  - Rowe, Lucy, 1978 (Box 74, Folder 1069)
  - Rowland, D. Wayne, 1964-1979 (Box 74, Folder 1070)
  - Roy, Andrew T. and Margaret, 1972-1979 (Box 74, Folder 1071)
  - Rugh, A. Douglas, 1961-1966 (Box 74, Folder 1072)
  - Rugh, Arthur - Scholarship, 1963-1966 (Box 74, Folder 1073)
  - Rugh, Charles E. and Sarah, 1959-1963 (Box 74, Folder 1074)
  - Runyan, Mary Edith, 1971-1974 (Box 74, Folder 1075)
  - Ruoss, G. Martin, 1966-1975 (Box 74, Folder 1076)
  - Rusk, Alexander and Anna, 1967-1979 (Box 74, Folder 1077)
  - Rutherford, James R., 1970-1979 (Box 74, Folder 1078)
  - Sa - Se (Box 74, Folder 1079-1081)
  - Sh - Sz (Box 75, Folder 1082-1089)
  - Sabah Christian College, Malaysia, 1963-1971 (Box 75, Folder 1090)
  - Sager, William, 1973 (Box 76, Folder 1091)
  - St. John's University, Shanghai, 1977 (Box 76, Folder 1092)
  - St. Louis Committee, 1974 (Box 76, Folder 1092)
  - Salares, Rafael, 1969-1972 (Box 76, Folder 1093)
  - Salonga, Jovito, 1978-1979 (Box 76, Folder 1094)
  - Salter, Kit, 1960-1969 (Box 76, Folder 1095)
  - Samonte, Abelardo, 1974-1978 (Box 76, Folder 1096)
  - Sample, John, 1962-1978 (Box 76, Folder 1097)
  - Sanders, Albert J., 1967-1979 (Box 76, Folder 1097)
  - Sanders, Philip H. and Florence, 1969-1979 (Box 76, Folder 1097)
  - San Diego, Carmelo C., 1972-1978 (Box 76, Folder 1098)
  - Saratoga Federated Church, CA, 1964-1979 (Box 76, Folder 1099)
  - Sawin, Margaret M., 1969-1974 (Box 76, Folder 1100)
  - Sayre, Francis B., 1966-1976 (Box 76, Folder 1100)
  - Scaff, Alvin H. and Marilee, 1969-1979 (Box 76, Folder 1101)
  - Scarsdale Community Baptist Church, NY, 1962-1975 (Box 76, Folder 1102)
  - Schaefer, Gail, 1964-1967 (Box 76, Folder 1103)
  - Schattschneider, David A., 1967-1968 (Box 76, Folder 1104)
  - Schecter, William H., 1964-1979 (Box 76, Folder 1105)
  - Scheid, D. Robert, 1978-1979 (Box 76, Folder 1106)
  - Scheide, William H., 1966-1979 (Box 76, Folder 1106)
  - Schoepflin, Paul and Ruth, 1964-1974 (Box 76, Folder 1107)
  - Schoyer, B. Preston, 1973-1975 (Box 76, Folder 1107)
  - Schultz, Lester, 1967-1978 (Box 76, Folder 1108)
  - Schwartz, Hans, 1973-1974 (Box 76, Folder 1108)
  - Science Research Associates, 1978 (Box 76, Folder 1109)
  - Scott, Ewing C., 1965-1979 (Box 76, Folder 1110)
  - Scott, George T., 1964-1979 (Box 77, Folder 1111)
  - Scott, Roderick and Agnes / Roderick Scott Memorial Chair, 1965-1979 (Box 77, Folder 1112)
  - Scovel, Frederick, 1965-1966 (Box 77, Folder 1113)
  - Seabury House, 1975-1978 (Box 77, Folder 1114)
  - Sears, Kathryne B., 1965-1979 (Box 77, Folder 1114)
  - Sears-Roebuck Foundation / Sears Roebuck Co., 1970-1979 (Box 77, Folder 1115)
  - Seaton, Ronald S., 1971-1974 (Box 77, Folder 1115)
  - Seattle Committee, 1971-1977 (Box 77, Folder 1116)
  - Seely, Albert, 1971-1979 (Box 77, Folder 1117-1119)
  - Seibert, Nicola, 1974-1978 (Box 77, Folder 1120)
  - Selch, Jean Harper, 1967 (Box 77, Folder 1121)
  - Sell, Ralph W., 1959-1976 (Box 77, Folder 1122)
  - Senturias, Alvaro L., 1971-1974 (Box 77, Folder 1123)
  - Seoul Foreign School, 1978 (Box 77, Folder 1124)
  - Seoul National University - Library survey (Frick), 1963 (Box 77, Folder 1124)
  - Seventh Day Adventists, 1963 (Box 77, Folder 1125)
  - Severinghaus, Leslie, 1961-1979 (Box 77, Folder 1126)
  - Severinghaus, Sheldon R., 1970-1979 (Box 77, Folder 1127)
  - Sharbough, J. W., 1964-1976 (Box 77, Folder 1128)
  - Shaw, Abbie Haylet, 1962-1967 (Box 77, Folder 1128)
  - Shaw, Yu-ming, 1972-1976 (Box 77, Folder 1129)
  - Shedd, Charles C., 1964-1979 (Box 77, Folder 1130)
  - Shen, Agatha Chiu, 1971-1979 (Box 77, Folder 1130)
  - Shen, Yao, 1969-1970 (Box 77, Folder 1131)
  - Shih, Thomas J. C. and Heather B., 1964-1972 (Box 77, Folder 1132)
  - Shorrock, Hallam, 1969-1970 (Box 77, Folder 1133)
  - Shropshire, Walter, 1962-1964 (Box 77, Folder 1133)
  - Shu, Frank M. S. and Grace, 1952-1972 (Box 78, Folder 1134-1136)
  - Shuyler, Harlan R., 1965-1974 (Box 78, Folder 1137)
  - Sie, Ping-teh (Georgiana), 1966-1978 (Box 78, Folder 1138)
  - Silliman, Frederick B., 1968 (Box 78, Folder 1139)
  - Silliman, Robert B., 1963-1977 (Box 78, Folder 1139)
  - Silliman, Sherwood E., 1962-1971 (Box 78, Folder 1139)
  - Silliman Alumni International, 1974-1977 (Box 78, Folder 1140)
  - Simmons, Shelby, 1973-1979 (Box 78, Folder 1141)
  - Sims, Albert G., 1968-1970 (Box 78, Folder 1142)
  - Singapore Junior College, 1969-1970 (Box 78, Folder 1142)
  - Skillman, John H., 1971-1979 (Box 78, Folder 1143)
  - Smidt, Merrita, 1974-1978 (Box 78, Folder 1144)
  - Smith, Carlton W., 1965-1973 (Box 78, Folder 1145)
  - Smith, Datus C., 1974-1979 (Box 78, Folder 1145)
  - Smith, Donald through Smith, Samuel R. (Box 79, Folder 1146-1152)